onlinecollegecourses.com 2018-10-19

# Privacy Policy - OnlineCollegeCourses.com

_Effective 2/2/16_

Thank you for visiting OnlineCollegeCourses.com. We appreciate your interest in our web content and services. This page details our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, including the way we use and share the information you submit. Because we may revise our terms at any time, we encourage you to visit this page periodically and review it to ensure you have a thorough understanding of our most up-to-date policies and terms of use.

By using OnlineCollegeCourses.com, we assume you agree to these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

## OnlineCollegeCourses.com’s Terms of Use

There are two categories of information that we collect. **Submitted information** is information that you voluntarily submit using the web forms on our site. We ask for your contact information, which includes your name, telephone number, email, and mailing address so we can provide requested services and recommend relevant, education-related products. We store your submitted information and share it with schools, affiliates, and third parties who can provide you with additional information about education-related products and services. 

By voluntarily submitting your information, you authorize OnlineCollegeCourses.com to:

  * Share your information, personally identifiable or otherwise, with schools, affiliated companies, and third parties.
  * Contact you via telephone, text message, email, or mail in accordance with all applicable laws in regard to relevant products and services regardless of any rights granted to you by the Do Not Call List for a period of time. You also authorise our affiliates and any third parties with which we share your information to contact you regardless of your status on the Do Not Call list. 
  * Release your information as needed with businesses that provide administrative services to our company.
  * Release your information as needed to abide by a subpoena, investigate alleged fraud, preserve our rights, protect the safety of others, respond to a legal request, or finalize a merger, sale, or acquisition of OnlineCollegeCourses.com with or to a third party.

If you do not wish to receive email communications from a particular school or third party, you can unsubscribe from future mailings at any time by clicking on the appropriate link in the body of the email. 

Whenever you interact with OnlineCollegeCourses.com, we also collect automatic information through the use of cookies. Cookies are small pieces of anonymous data that websites store in a user’s browser. Most websites use cookies to help improve the overall user experience of the site. The kind of data that cookies collect include a user’s IP address, operating system, and web browser. 

By using our website, you acknowledge and consent to our use of cookies. We use Google Analytics to help us track visitor data. You can learn more about Google’s privacy policy here: http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html.

Cookies allow us to:

  * Tailor advertisements for potential customers. 
  * Gather demographic data to optimize our outreach efforts. 
  * Track conversions of our marketing endeavors. 
  * Audit our leads to ensure relevancy, accuracy and validity of submitted information. 

Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information, but you have the right to remove them from your web browser at any time. Depending on your privacy settings, you may have to remove them every time you surf the web. You also have the right to opt out of receiving certain personalized advertisements. Simply visit the websites of the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance and follow the prompts to unsubscribe. 

## How to Contact Us

Thank you for your interest in our products and services. If you have any questions or concerns about our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, please contact us using the appropriate web form on our site. 

## Find the perfect course for you in just 3 easy steps
